(Howard:)You're awful quiet.
Everything OK?
(Sheldon:)Not really.
(Sheldon:)I had a bit
of an embarrassing evening.
(Howard:)Me, too. What happened?
(Sheldon:)I drank alcohol
(Sheldon:)and may have left an unfortunate
voice mail for Stephen Hawking.
(Howard:)I wouldn't worry about it.
(Howard:)He's got a pretty good
sense of humor.
(Sheldon:)I hope so.
(Sheldon:)What happened to you
last night?
(Howard:)Well, turns out
(Howard:)I'd already met the girl
Raj is seeing
(Howard:)when I did a number
on her bathroom.
(Howard:)And that number was two.
(Sheldon:)Well, you know,
I've always been a fan
(Sheldon:)of a story told
by Attar of Nishapur,
(Sheldon:)about a king,
who assembled a group of wise men
(Sheldon:)to create a ring that would
make him happy when he was sad.